<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alma Fiesta 2k20</string>
    <string name="im1">"http://2019.almafiesta.com/images/Headbang_lineup.jpeg"</string>
    <string name="im2">"http://2019.almafiesta.com/images/Leela_Dance1.jpg"</string>
    <string name="im3">"http://2019.almafiesta.com/images/Naalayak.jpg"</string>
    <string name="im4">"http://2019.almafiesta.com/images/aron-chupa.jpg"</string>
    <string name="not1">null</string>
    <string name="not2">null</string>
    <string name="username">null</string>
    <string name="shadez">"Each participant will be given maximum of 2 hours to complete their sketch.\nAll participants must bring their college identity cards.\nParticipants without identity cards will not be allowed to participate.\nAny pencil sketch is allowed in the event.\nMaterials provided: Drawing sheets, Pencils, Erasers and Sharpeners.\nThe decision of the judge shall be FINAL and BINDING."</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="mun">mun rules</string>
    <string name="euphony">"Rounds : 1 Round\nEligibility : Participation in the form of a band of 3-10 members only.\n• The use of laptops or mixers or any other digital modifiers is prohibited.\n• Each band will be allotted a total of 30 minutes (Amps on to Amps off. Inclusive of sound check).\n• A drum kit, 5-6 microphones and sufficient input lines will be provided on stage. Other instruments are to be brought by participants.\n• Original compositions are welcome.\n• Medleys and mashups are allowed, provided the performance comes under the given time limit.\n• Obscenity and vulgarity of any manner is not allowed in neither the lyrics nor in gestures.\n• Judges’ decision will be final and binding.\n• No pre-recorded music is allowed."</string>
    <string name="track">"Rounds : 2 rounds (Qualifying Round and Final Round)\nEligibility : Solo Performance on Karaoke Track\nFirst round is a knock out round. In this round, the contestant is free to sing a song of his/her choice.\nBased on the performance in this round, participants will be selected for the final round.\nFinal round includes two performances by each finalist - one of the finalist’s choice, one of the judges’ choice. (To be selected from a list of 3 songs provided by the participant).\n Every contestant must bring his/her own karaoke tracks.\nHe/she must bring at least 5 tracks (2 for the participant’s choice rounds and three for the judges’ choice round).\n• All the contestants should bring the tracks in a CD/Pen drive.\n• Language of performance is restricted to Hindi and English only.\n No pre-recorded music is allowed.\n Judges’ decision will be final and binding."</string>
    <string name="duetto">"Rounds : 2 rounds (Qualifying Round and Final Round)\nEligibility : Duet Performance on Karaoke Track\n First round is a knock out round. In this round, the contestants are free to sing a song of their choice.\n Based on the performance in this round, groups will be selected for the final round.\n Final round includes two performances by each selected group-one of group’s choice and one of judges’ choice (to be selected from a list of 3 songs provided by the group)\nEvery group must bring their own karaoke tracks.\n Each participating group must bring at least 5 tracks (2 for the Contestant’s choice rounds and three for the judges’ choice round).\nAll the participants should bring the tracks in a CD/Pen drive.\n Language of performance is restricted to Hindi and English only." </string>
    <string name="unplugged">"Rounds : 1 Round\nEligibility : Solo performance on any instrument\nParticipants are not allowed to use laptops or mixers or any other digital modifiers.\nDrum kit will be provided by the organizing team on stage for drummers.\nThe on-stage time limit is 10 minutes. (amps on to amps off).\nParticipant may lend his/her voice if they wish to. The judging, however will only be based on the instrumental performance.\nOriginal compositions are welcome.\nNo pre-recorded music is allowed."</string>
    <string name="upbeat">"Rounds : 1 Round\nEligibility : Participation in the form of a group of 2-7 members only.\n Participants are not allowed to use laptops or mixers or any other digital modifiers.\nOnly acoustic and semi - acoustic instruments are allowed. Synthesizer and bass guitar are allowed.\nEach group will be allotted 15 minutes for performance (inclusive of sound check).\nA drum kit, 5-6 microphones and sufficient input lines will be provided on stage. Other instruments are to be brought by participants.\nJudging will be based on overall group performance.\n Original compositions are welcome.\nNo pre-recorded music is allowed.\nJudges’ decision will be final and binding."</string>
    <string name="facepainting">"It will be a team competition with one model and 1 painter. Only the painter needs to register for the event.\nIt’ll be an open theme competition.\nAll participants must carry the identity card of their respective colleges.\nParticipants without identity cards will not be allowed to participate.\nWinners in Fine arts genre will receive cash prize of 5k and goodies worth 30k.\nEach team will be given maximum 3 hours to complete their painting.\nSpecial Effects may be used including:- False eyelashes, glitter.\nMasks, elastic or tape are not allowed.\nBasic equipments like water colour and brushes will be given, but the participants themselves need to bring any other equipment like sponges and acrylic colours if they wish.\nJudges decision will be FINAL and BINDING on all participants."</string>
    <string name="rab">"There will be a single round.\nThe duo couple will be given 2-6 minutes to perform.\nThe audio track must be submitted in a pen-drive or hard disk in .mp3 format, at the time of confirmation of registration at the event venue.\nAll participants must bring their college identity cards.\nSong must be brought by the participating team in a CD, DVD or Pen drive-if they don’t, disqualified.\nThe songs must not contain any illicit or offensive language.\nAny obscene action in the dance is prohibited and will lead to Disqualification.\nAll props, costumes and make-up will have to be brought by the teams.\nNo props will be provided by the organizers. In case of special prop requirement such as chairs, the teams will have to inform the organizers in advance.\nUse of flame or fluid on stage, lighting of candles, matches or cigarettes is strictly NOT allowed and will lead in Disqualification of the team."</string>
    <string name="ripout">"There will be a single round.\nThe individual will be given 3-6 minutes to perform.\nThe individual must bring the audio track in a pen-drive or hard disk in .mp3 format and submit it at the time of confirmation of registration at the event venue.\nThe songs must not contain any illicit or offensive language.\nAny obscene action in the dance is prohibited and will lead to Disqualification.\nAll participants must bring their college identity cards. Participants without identity cards will not be allowed to participate.\nUse of flame or fluid on stage, lighting of candles, matches or cigarettes is strictly NOT allowed and will lead in Disqualification.\nParticipants have to arrange for their own props, costumes and make-up. No props will be provided by the organizers. However, in case of special prop requirement such as chairs the participants will have to inform the organizers in advance.\nIn case of malfunctioning of any equipment provided, the participant will be allowed to repeat the performance or start from the point of disruption as he/she chooses, with the consent of the judges."</string>
    <string name="topsy">"2 Rounds – Qualifying and Final\n Stage setting time: 1.5 minutes (maximum).\nTime limit: 5-10 minutes. Exceeding this will lead to penalization in marks.\nTeam limit : 22 + 2 CAs(for light and sound)\nAll dance forms are allowed.\nUse of water, fire and glass is prohibited.\nAudio track to be brought in .mp3 format, in a pen drive or a hard disk and should be submitted by group on the registration desk.\nThe songs must not contain any illicit or offensive language.\n Any obscene action in the dance is prohibited and will lead to Disqualification.\nAny specific requirements regarding lights and smoke must be discussed with coordinator well in advance.\nUse of Voice Over(s) is allowed."</string>
    <string name="faceoff">"Each contestant will be given a time limit of 8 minutes.\nThe contestants are allowed to do anything like Stand-up comedy, Mimicry, mime, Impromptu or any other skill they wish to perform.\nThis is strictly a Solo act competition.\nThe language of act is strictly prohibited to English/Hindi.\nThe contestants’ performances are scrutinized and are judged based upon the creativity, stage presence and interest shown in entertaining the crowd.\nInstrumental music is allowed but the participants will have to bring their own instruments.\nMicrophones, lights and laptop to play sounds will be provided.\nNaked flames or live animals are not allowed on stage.\nParticipants will have to bring their own music in CD/PD.\nThe judges might ask the contestants to perform something on the spot to test their skills.\nThe top three performances judged the jury gets to be the winners of the competition." </string>
    <string name="ncircled">"Group of maximum 22 members have to perform a Street Play of any genre.\nThe maximum time permitted for each play is 30 minutes.\nEach group will be judged mainly on performance, script and various other aspects.\nMusic accompanists are included in the team size stated above.\nTeams are expected to perform at the open air venue with audience on all sides.\nOnly live music is allowed. Teams will have to bring their own instruments.\nAny vulgarity/obscenity will be strictly penalized and may lead to disqualification.\nAny kind of fluids, live animals, flame, heavy and sharp objects or any other harmful material is STRICTLY not allowed.\nTeams will be heavily penalised if they exceed the time limit.\nLogistics should be self-arranged.\nEach group will be judged mainly on performance, script and various other aspects."</string>
    <string name="spotlight">"\nGroup have to perform a Stage Play of any genre.\nTeam Limit: 15 members + 3 CAs (for light and sound).\nThe minimum time for stage play is 15 minutes and maximum time permitted for each play is 45 minutes.\nLanguage of the play can be Hindi/English. Mime is allowed.\nPre-registration is necessary before the date of the event.\nRecorded vocals are not allowed, only music is allowed.\nThe teams will have to bring their own music in CDs/PDs.\nNo naked flames or live animals are allowed on stage.\nSound and Lights will be arranged by the Organisation.\nNo other logistics will be provided from the Organisation. The costumes and logistics must be self-arranged.\nUse of foul language or any obscenity will lead to immediate disqualification.\nIn case of malfunctioning of any equipment provided, group will be allowed to repeat their performance from the last point of disruption. The decision will be as per judges’ direction for how to give grace time."</string>
    <string name="shortf">\nThe team size can be maximum 20 people including actors.\nThe maximum time limit for the short film will be 15 minutes.\nThe movie should either be in Hindi or English or both. No other languages are permitted.\nThe video may be taken with any device.\nThe theme of the competition is \'Youngistaan : A Montage Of Dreams\'.\nThe short films have to be submitted either Online/Offline by 12th of January.\nFor Online submission share the Google Drive link to publicrelations@almafiesta.com\nObscenity of any kind is not allowed and shall lead to disqualification.\nThe decision of the judges and the organizing team will be final.\nAlma Fiesta reserves the right to use the video entries on social media (suitable credits will be given to the people responsible for the creation of the content).\nThe winning entries will be published on our Facebook page."</string>
    <string name="pic">Team Size: 1 member.\nSubmission deadline: 11:59 pm each day during the 3 days of fest. The online submission link will be shared before the fest.\nPhotographs must be taken inside the campus and during the events only.\nThe more diversity in photos brings you more points.\nParticipant can submit at max 5 photos each day.\nPhotographs must contain EXIF data.\nParticipants must submit both raw images (CR2/NEF/SR2, etc) and edited images (jpeg/jpg).\nDo not include your credentials (Name, Watermark, Date, etc) in the frame of the photograph.\nPhotographs should not contain any objectionable content. If found, entry will be disqualified by judge’s consent.\nOnly global editing is allowed.\nAlma Fiesta reserves the right to use the entries (suitable credits will be given to the people responsible for the creation of the content).</string>
    <string name="docu">The maximum team size is 10 members.\nThe teams will have to come to the campus and shoot for three days.\nThe maximum duration for the documentary is 10 minutes.\nThe participants will have to submit their videos offline.\nThe participants must be present at the specified venue during the judging of their submission.\nJudging criteria includes fest coverage, content, editing and overall impact of the video.\nAlma Fiesta reserves the right to use the video entries on social media.\nThe top documentaries will be featured in Alma Fiesta after movie, so you may be asked to submit the unedited shots.</string>
    <string name="samvad">"चरण 1 : समूह-चर्चा –\nसमूह चर्चा में प्रतिभागियों को 4-4 के समूह में बाँट दिया जायेगा।\nचर्चा के लिए एक विषय दिया जायेगा जो कि किसी भी प्रकार का हो सकता है।\nस्व-विचार हेतु 2 मिनट तथा समूह चर्चा हेतु 10 मिनट दिए जायेंगे।\nप्रतियोगिता के प्रथम चरण के प्रदर्शन के आधार पर 10 प्रतिभागी अंतिम चरण के लिए चुने जायेंगे।\nचरण 2 : वाद-विवाद –\nयह एक वाद-विवाद प्रतियोगिता होगी जिसके नियम पहले चरण की समाप्ति के बाद बताये जायेंगे।\n्व-विचार हेतु 2 मिनट तथा समूह चर्चा हेतु 10 मिनट दिए जायेंगे।\nसामान्य निर्देश :-\nप्रतियोगिता में चर्चा का समय सीमा से अधिक होने पर उस चर्चा में उपस्थित सभी प्रतिभागियों का नकारात्मक अंकन किया जाएगा ।\nिर्णायक मण्डली का निर्णय अंतिम होगा । "</string>
    <string name="drishtikon">"चरण 1 :\nप्रतिभागी को सर्वप्रथम दिए गये विषयों में से किसी एक का चुनाव करना होगा\nिषय पर सोचने हेतु प्रतिभागी को 30 सेकंड का समय दिया जाएगा\nप्रतिभागी को 2 मिनट में विचार व्यक्त करने होंगे अपने निष्कर्ष को 30 सेकंड में व्यक्त करना होगा\nचरण 2 :\nयह भी एक आशुभाषण प्रतियोगिता होगी, जिसके नियम और दिशानिर्देश प्रथम चरण की समाप्ति के समय स्पष्ट किये जायेंगे ।\nसामान्य निर्देश :-\nरतियोगिता में तय सीमा के बाद भी बोलते रहने पर नकारात्मक अंकन किया जाएगा ।\nिर्णायक मण्डली का निर्णय अंतिम होगा । "</string>
    <string name="poetry">It is an individual competition.\nOnly original work of the participant is entertained. Plagiarism of any kind leads to a direct disqualification.\nThe poem may be in either Hindi or English.\nPoems need to be submitted by 11:59 p.m., 11th January at am34@iitbbs.ac.in\nA participant can recite a maximum of 1 poem only.\nAll entries should be original compositions in English or Hindi.\nTime limit for each performance - 5 min\nObscenity of any kind is not allowed.\nParticipants are requested to carry their own props, if any to be used by them during performance.\nParticipants may carry a piece of paper or phone which they may refer to while reciting but reciting without help shall be an advantage.\nThe Judges’ decision shall be final in all matters pertaining to participation and organization of the competition.<b>Judging Criteria</b>\n•	Stage presence\n•	Voice and articulation\n•	Performance \n•	Content\n•   Body language\n<b>Note:</b> The judging criteria may vary slightly based on the preference of the judges, however in this event, the new criteria shall be duly announced prior to the event."</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
